openttd.org 2019-04-14

# OpenTTD | Policy

Your privacy is important to OpenTTD. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that OpenTTD collects, and the ways in which OpenTTD uses that personal information.

### Personal Information Collection

OpenTTD may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

  * information that you provide for the purpose of registering with the website (including name and e-mail address);
  * any other information that you send to OpenTTD.

### Using Personal Information

OpenTTD may use your personal information to:

  * administer this website;
  * personalise the website for you;
  * enable your access to and use of the website services;
  * send you notifications

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, OpenTTD may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

### Security of your Data

OpenTTD will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

OpenTTD will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers.

### Cross-border Data Transfers

Information that OpenTTD collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which OpenTTD operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the Internet and may be available around the world.

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

### Updating this Statement

OpenTTD may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

### Other Websites

This website contains links to other websites.

OpenTTD is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

### Contact OpenTTD

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or OpenTTD's treatment of your personal information, please write by email to [info@openttd.org](mailto:info@openttd.org).

### This Privacy Statement

This privacy statement is based on an original template created by [website-contracts.co.uk](http://website-contracts.co.uk/) and distributed by [freenetlaw.com](http://freenetlaw.com/).

### About Cookies

Cookies are information packets sent by web servers to web browsers, and stored by the web browsers.

The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables web servers to identify and track web browsers.

There are two main kinds of cookies: session cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies are deleted from your computer when you close your browser, whereas persistent cookies remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach their expiry date.

### Cookies on our Website

OpenTTD uses the following cookies on this website, for the following purposes:

  * Keeping track of customisation wishes of the user on the different websites.
  * Allowing automatic login at different websites.

### Refusing Cookies

Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies.

In Internet Explorer, you can refuse all cookies by clicking "Tools", "Internet Options", "Privacy", and selecting 'Block all cookies" using the sliding selector.

In Firefox, you can adjust your cookies settings by clicking "Tools", "Options" and "Privacy".

Blocking cookies will have a negative impact upon the usability of some websites.

### This Cookies Policy

This cookies policy is based on an original template created by [template-contracts.co.uk](http://template-contracts.co.uk/) and distributed by [freenetlaw.com](http://freenetlaw.com/).
